http://mjsa.polygon.net/jwl/public/about/privacy-policy-en.jsp

Login
Username:
Password:
Forgot Your Password?
The Polygon Privacy Statement
Polygon recognizes the importance of the privacy issue in use of the Internet and World Wide Web. Information which you provide to us either directly (through on-line forms, or via email or fax) or indirectly (data normally collected on traffic to this site or other third party sites managed by Polygon) is covered by our Privacy Policy.
Information About Website Visits
We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability, and for marketing purposes.
We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We may send a cookie which may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognize your computer when you visit our website, and to personalize our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies.
We may use anonymous cookies to record non-personal information such as website activity, date and time of visit, and domain type. We may use this information for retargeting purposes. Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
The Polygon Privacy Policy
Polygon holds in confidence all information (such as name, address, and phone number) given to us by customers and visitors to this site. We will not sell or release this information to any organization outside of Polygon without your knowledge and consent. Information you provide is used to support your customer relationship with Polygon, and may be shared on a restricted basis with agents directly performing services for us. Polygon may from time to time contact you with news about products or special offers, which we feel, could be of interest you. You may at any time ask for more information about our privacy policy, or request that we remove your name from our mailing list by calling 1-800-221-4435 or emailing support@polygon.net. We reserve the right to retain certain customer information, which relates to billing, account status, and product warranties.
Try it For Free
Success Stories
"Our sales are up. Our revenues are up. And our profits are up. The secret is Polygon."
